<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.sheldon.idea.plugin.asynctest-caller</id>
    <name>AsyncTest Caller</name>
    <version>1.0.0.212.0</version>
    <vendor email="leesheldonparsons@gmail.com" url="https://github.com/SheldonParsons">Sheldon</vendor>

    <description>
        <![CDATA[
        <h2>AsyncTest Caller</h2>
        <p>
            <strong>AsyncTest Caller</strong>
            is an IntelliJ IDEA plugin designed to scan
            <strong>Spring Web projects</strong>
            and automatically extract API endpoint information.
        </p>
        <p>
            The plugin analyzes Spring MVC / Spring Boot controllers, collects structured
            interface metadata (such as paths, HTTP methods, and related models), and
            synchronizes this data to the <strong>AsyncTest platform</strong> in a
            well-organized, structured format.
        </p>
        <p>
            By automating API discovery and synchronization, AsyncTest Caller helps keep
            your AsyncTest interface definitions <strong>consistent, up-to-date, and tightly
            aligned with your source code</strong>, reducing manual maintenance and
            integration errors.
        </p>
        <h3>Key Features</h3>
        <ul>
            <li>🔍 Scan Spring Web / Spring Boot controller interfaces</li>
            <li>🧩 Build structured API and data model information</li>
            <li>🔄 Synchronize interface data with the AsyncTest platform</li>
            <li>⚡ Improve consistency between backend code and test definitions</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            AsyncTest Caller is ideal for teams that want to <strong>bridge the gap between
            Spring-based backend services and AsyncTest</strong>, enabling efficient API
            management and automated test integration.
        </p>
        <h3>Compatibility & Supported Versions</h3>
        <p>
            AsyncTest Caller is engineered to ensure broad compatibility across the JetBrains ecosystem.
            It is compiled with <strong>Java 17</strong> compatibility to support older IDE versions while remaining
            fully functional on the latest releases.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <strong>Minimum Requirement:</strong>
                IntelliJ IDEA 2021.2.1 (Build <code>212+</code>)
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Maximum Requirement:</strong>
                None (Supports 2022.x, 2023.x, 2024.x, and future releases)
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>Verified Versions:</strong>
                The plugin has been verified against:
                <ul>
                    <li>IntelliJ IDEA 2022.3</li>
                    <li>IntelliJ IDEA 2023.1</li>
                    <li>IntelliJ IDEA 2024.1+</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            Whether you are maintaining legacy projects on an older IDE or using the cutting-edge EAP version, AsyncTest
            Caller has you covered.
        </p>
        <p><br/></p>
<h2>Privacy Policy</h2>
<p><b>Last Updated:</b> December 23, 2025</p>
<p>
    By using the <b>AsyncTest Caller</b> plugin, you verify that you agree to the following terms regarding data collection and usage.
</p>

<h3>1. Data Collection & Transmission</h3>
<ul>
    <li><b>Source Code Scanning:</b> The plugin scans your project files locally to identify API definitions (e.g., Spring Controllers).</li>
    <li><b>Data Upload:</b> When you explicitly click "Upload" or "Sync", API metadata is transmitted to the AsyncTest server.</li>
    <li><b>Destination:</b> Data is sent <b>only</b> to the server URL you configured in <i>Settings > Tools > AsyncTest Caller</i>.</li>
</ul>

<h3>2. User Control</h3>
<ul>
    <li>No background uploads occur without your explicit action or configuration.</li>
    <li>You have full control over the server URL and Access Token.</li>
</ul>

<h3>3. Data Usage</h3>
<p>The transmitted data is used solely to generate test cases and sync API definitions on the AsyncTest platform.</p>

<p>For more details, please contact us via our GitHub(https://github.com/SheldonParsons/AsyncTest-Caller) repository.</p>
        ]]>
    </description>

    <category>Web</category>

    <idea-version since-build="212.0"/>

    <change-notes>
        <![CDATA[
    <h3>v1.0.0 - Initial Release</h3>
    <p>🎉 First public release of <b>AsyncTest Caller</b>!</p>
    <p><b>Key Features:</b></p>
    <ul>
        <li><b>Spring Boot Integration:</b> Automatically parse <code>@RequestMapping</code>, headers, and params from Java controllers.</li>
        <li><b>One-Click Generation:</b> Quickly generate async test cases directly from the IDE editor.</li>
        <li><b>API Dashboard:</b> Dedicated ToolWindow to manage and visualize your API endpoints.</li>
        <li><b>Seamless Sync:</b> Upload test cases to the AsyncTest platform with configurable settings.</li>
        <li>Compatible with IntelliJ IDEA 2022.3 and later (Java 17+).</li>
    </ul>
    ]]>
    </change-notes>

    <depends optional="true" config-file="java-support.xml">com.intellij.modules.java</depends>
    <depends optional="true" config-file="maven-support.xml">org.jetbrains.idea.maven</depends>
    <depends optional="true" config-file="gradle-support.xml">com.intellij.gradle</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.properties</depends>
    <depends>org.jetbrains.plugins.yaml</depends>


</idea-plugin>
